peltiertech.com 2017-09-02

# Peltier Tech Blog Privacy Policy - Peltier Tech Blog

Thursday, August 3, 2017   
Peltier Technical Services, Inc., [Copyright © 2017](https://peltiertech.com/copyright-and-licensing/ "Copyright and Licensing"), All rights reserved.  

## Privacy

I respect your privacy and I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at peltiertech.com. The following discloses how I gather and disseminate information for this Blog.

## RSS Feeds and Email Updates

If a user wishes to subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates, I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party. You will never be spammed by me – ever.

## Log Files and Stats

Like most blogging platforms I use Google Analytics to analyze traffic. Google stores information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, platform used, date/time stamp, track user’s movement in the whole, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. I have no access to personally identifiable information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This blog doesn’t use cookies. However, some of my business partners use cookies on this site (for example – advertisers). I can’t access or control these cookies once the advertisers have set them.

## Links

This Blog contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. I advise my users to be aware of this when they leave this blog and to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this blog.

## Advertisers

I use third-party advertising companies, including Google and Amazon, to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These advertisers may use cookies which are collected by the advertising companies; I do not have access to this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please check the advertisers websites for respective privacy policies.

Most advertising links on these pages are paid, either on a per-pageview basis to be hosted on this web site, or on a per-purchase basis for affiliate sales links. The commissions are not large, and I would not host ads for these affiliate products and books if I didn’t believe they were good products and worth the price.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns please contact me at [jon@peltiertech.com](mailto:jon@peltiertech.com). This privacy policy was updated August 2017.

**Posted:** Thursday, August 3rd, 2017 under .  
 **Tags:** .  
[**Comments:**](https://peltiertech.com/privacy-policy/#respond) none
